In recent years, the food industry has increased its use of labels.
近年来，食品行业越来越多地使用标签。
Whether the labels say ‘non-GMO’ or ‘no sugar’ or ‘zero carbohydrates’, consumers are increasingly demanding more information about what’s in their food.
无论标签上写的是“非转基因”“无糖”还是“零碳水化合物”，消费者都越来越要求获得更多信息，了解自己所吃的食品里有什么。
One report found that 39 percent of consumers would switch from the brands they currently buy to others that provide clearer, more accurate product information.
一份报告发现，39%的消费者会放弃目前购买的品牌，转而选择能提供更清晰、更准确的产品信息的其他品牌。
Food manufacturers are responding to the report with new labels to meet that demand, and they’re doing so with an eye towards giving their products an advantage over the competition, and bolstering profits.
食品生产商正推出新标签来回应这份报告，以满足这一需求；而他们这样做，是着眼于让自己的产品比竞争对手更具优势，并提高利润。
This strategy makes intuitive sense.
这一策略从直觉上讲得通。
If consumers say they want transparency, tell them exactly what is in your product.
如果消费者说希望信息透明，那就确切地告诉他们你的产品里有什么。
That is simply supplying a certain demand.
这只不过是在满足某种需求。
But the marketing strategy in response to this consumer demand has gone beyond articulating what is in a product, to labeling what is NOT in the food.
但为回应消费者的这一需求而制定的营销策略，已经超出了清楚说明产品里有什么的范围，发展到标注食品里“没有”什么。
These labels are known as “absence claims” labels, and they represent an emerging labeling trend that is detrimental to both the consumers who purchase the products and the industry that supplies them.
这类标签被称为“不含声明”标签，代表着一种新兴的标注趋势，这种趋势既有损于购买这些产品的消费者，也有损于供应这些产品的行业。
For example, Hunt’s put a “non-GMO” label on its canned crushed tomatoes a few years ago—despite the fact that at the time there was no such thing as a GMO tomato on the market.
例如，几年前，Hunt’s在其罐装番茄碎上贴了“非转基因”标签，尽管当时市场上根本没有转基因番茄这种东西。
Some dairy companies are using the “non-GMO” label on their milk—another label that creates unnecessary fear around food—despite the fact that all milk is naturally GMO-free.
一些乳品公司正在自家牛奶上使用“非转基因”标签（这又是一个让人对食品产生不必要恐惧的标签），尽管所有牛奶天然就不含转基因成分。
While creating labels that play on consumer fears and misconceptions about their food may give a company a temporary marketing advantage over competing products on the grocery aisle, in the long term this strategy will have just the opposite effect: by injecting fear into the discourse about our food, we run the risk of eroding consumer trust in not just a single product, but the entire food business.
虽然制作标签来利用消费者对食品的恐惧和误解，可能会让一家公司在超市货架上暂时获得胜过竞争产品的营销优势，但从长远来看，这种策略将产生恰恰相反的效果：我们在有关自己所吃食品的讨论中注入恐惧，就会冒侵蚀消费者信任的风险，受到侵蚀的将不只是对某一种产品的信任，还有对整个食品行业的信任。
Eventually, it becomes a question in consumers’ minds: Were these foods ever safe?
最终，消费者心里会产生一个疑问：这些食品曾经安全过吗？
By purchasing and consuming these types of products, have I already done some kind of harm to my family or the planet?
购买和食用这类产品，我是不是已经对家人或地球造成了某种伤害？
For food manufacturers, it will mean damaged consumer trust and lower sales for everyone.
对食品生产商来说，这将意味着消费者信任受损，大家的销量都会下降。
And this isn’t just supposition.
而这并不只是猜测。
A recent study found that absence claims labels can create a stigma around foods even when there is no scientific evidence that they cause harm.
最近的一项研究发现，“不含声明”标签可能会使食品蒙上污名，即使并没有科学证据表明这些食品会造成危害。
It’s clear that food manufacturers must tread carefully when it comes to using absence claims.
显然，说到使用“不含声明”，食品生产商必须谨慎行事。
In addition to the likely negative long-term impact on sales, this verbal trick sends a message that innovations in farming and food processing are unwelcome, eventually leading to less efficiency, fewer choices for consumers, and, ultimately, more costly food products.
这种文字把戏除了很可能对销量造成长期的负面影响，还传递出农业和食品加工领域的创新不受欢迎的信息，终将导致效率降低、消费者的选择减少，并最终使食品更加昂贵。
If we allow this kind of labeling to continue, we will all lose.
如果任由这种标注做法继续下去，我们所有人都会是输家。